

DHARANIKUMAR K

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone

+91-9952638437



Email

dharanfsd@gmail.com



Address

Dusi, Kancheepuram, Tamilnadu



MY SKILLS

- HTML
- (>) CSS
- O BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NODEJS
- **EXPRESS JS**
- MONGODB
- AWS



LANGUAGE

- Tamil
- English





PROFILE INFO

To work with a progressive organization in which I can contribute my technical skills and experience to achieve the objectives of the organization with the attribute of time and quality at the same time to enhance my own productivity.

EDUCATION

\bigcirc	Diploma In Automobile	2009-2011
	Engineering	

Dusi Polytechnic College, Dusi

2013-2016 **B.E - Mechanical Engineering** (2)

Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College of Engineering. - AMACE Vadamavandhal-Kancheepuram

\odot **MBA - Supply Chain Management** 2018-2019

University of Madras - Chennai

CERTIFICATE

2022-2023 \odot **Full Stack Development**

Guvi - Chennai

WORK EXPERIENCE

 \odot **Quality Trainee** 2011-2013

Hyundai Mobis - Chennai

Quality Engineer \odot 2016-2018

Rockman - Cheyyar

(2)**Quality Engineer** 2018-2019

TVS Sundaram Clayton - Chennai

Entrepreneur (\mathbf{b}) 2019-Till Now

STARFLIT- Dusi, Kancheepuram

MY ACHIEVEMENT

- Reduce the Rejection 10% to 3% by process (2)optimization in HPDC along with product design.
- (2)Conduct TS 16949: 2002 System Internal Audit, MRM.